Pierre Eugène du Simitière collection LCP.DuSimitiere
Library Company of Philadelphia
- Series III. Papers relating to Pennsylvania, the Carolinas, etc., 1753-1778; [965] (Box 2)
  - Extracts from de Boffun and Daubenton's L'Histoire Naturelle about elephant bones found in America, 1753-1778 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Longetivity of the people in North America and the West Indies", 1669-1779 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Graveston inscriptions, 1753-1778 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Extracts from Gentleman's Magazine, American Weekly Mercury, and the Pennsylvania Gazette, 1734, 1738, 1737 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Drawings of Redwood Library and Old Academy and Charity School, 1753-1778 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Watercolor of the bay of Newport, Rhode Island, 1753-1778 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Etchings of unidentified buildings, 1753-1778 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Extracts from public records of New Haven, Connecticut, 1753-1778 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Impressions of coins, 1753-1778 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Series IV. Indian Treaties, 1721-1756, [966] (Box 3)
  The series “Indian Treaties, 1721-1756” contains sixty documents that relate to colonists' affairs with Native Americans prior to the Revolution. Heavily documented in the series are the minutes of councils; correspondence; and treatise between the English in Philadelphia and New York and the Five Nations, and later the Six Nations. Included in the series are treaties and their relevant correspondence from Conrad Weiser, William Shirley, James DeLancey, Robert Hunter Morris, and others. These documents reveal remarkable agreements between the Native Americans and the colonists, including numerous agreements involving the trade of goods and land, and agreements on the hunting of game. Also included are the testimonies of two traders describing French mistreatment of Native American traders, correspondence and other documents relating to the French and Indian Wars, and documents about Native American and colonist conflicts. An interesting document about an English and Native American conflict is the Petition to Lieutenant Governor Robert Morris of Pennsylvania from October 20, 1755, in which settlers petitioned the governor for aid and ammunition as a result of Native Americans attacks. The petition also contains testimonies from settlers who had been involved in the attacks.
  The documents in this series are originals and copies. While the dates that the copies were made is unknown, the dates of the original documents from which copies were made span the years 1721 to 1756. This series is arranged in chronological order.
  - Minutes of Council held at Philadelphia, 1721 March 6 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of testimony given in the Philadelphia Court regarding an Indian killed by Edmund Cartlidge, 1722 March 10 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Address of Governor Sir William Keith to Council, 1722 April 16 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Minutes of councils with Indians at Conestoga, 1722 April 6-7 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Report made to Council in Philadelphia regarding a message sent to the Five Nations, 1722 July 30 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Minutes of a council at Philadelphia, 1723 January 25-28 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Treaty with Five Nations made at Philadelphia, 1727 July 3-5 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1728 April 18 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Two Indian Treaties (pamphlet), 1728 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of a council at Philadelphia, 1728 October 10 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Treaty made at Philadelphia, 1729 May 26-27 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Petition to the Governor of New York, 1731 September 25 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
  - Minutes of the Commission for Indian Affairs, Albany, 1731 September 25 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
  - Testimony of Jonah Davenport, an Indian trader, before Lieutenant Governor Gordon in Philadelphia, 1731 October 29 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
  - Testimony of James Letort, an Indian trader, before Lieutenant Governor Gordon in Philadelphia, 1731 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Treaty made with Six Nations at Philadelphia, 1732 August-September (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Treaty between Shawnee Indians and Pennsylvania made in Philadelphia, 1732 September 30-October 7 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Treaty with Six Nations made at Philadelphia, 1736 September 28 October 14 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Minutes of meeting of Council and chiefs of the Cayuga Indians, 1741, October 14 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Minutes of conference between Council and Six Nations, 1742 June 30-July 12 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Treaty made at Lancaster, Pennsylvania with Six Nations, 1744 June 22, 25-30 and July 2-4 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Minutes of council held at Philadelphia, 1744 August 21 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Petition by Sheridan, a trader in Loogane, to the General Intendant of the French Islands of America, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Letter from Conrad Weiser, Heidelberg, 1746 January 24 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Minutes of council held at Philadelphia in the Supreme Court, 1749 July 1-6 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Three letters from Conrad Weiser to Richard Peters regarding his trip to meet various tribes of Indians, 1744 August 6-12 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Journal of Conrad Weiser's journey to Albany with a message from the Governor of Pennsylvania to the Six Nations, 1751 June 10-July 27 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Letter from Richard Peters to Pennsylvania Assembly, 1752 February 6 (Box 3, Folder 28a)
  - Report of Committee of Representatives in Philadelphia, 1752 February 25 (Box 3, Folder 28b)
  - Instructions of Governor James Hamilton to John Patten, 1753 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Extract from letter of Mr. Smith to Governor [William] Shirley, Cape Cod, 1753 December 24 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Governor Robert Dinwiddie to Governor [James] Hamilton, Williamsburg, 1752 March 1 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Letter from Governor William Shirley to Governor [James] Hamilton, Boston, 1754 March 4 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Letter from Governor Robert Dinwiddie to Governor [James] Hamilton, Williamsburg, 1754 March 21 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Testimony regarding French mistreatment of Indian traders, circa 1754 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Testimony regarding French mistreatment of an Indian trader, 1754 March 22 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Letter from Hetchen Holland to Governor [James] De Lancey, undated (Box 3, Folder 36-38)
  - Letter from Governor James De Lancey to Governor [James] Hamilton, New York, 1754 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 36-38)
  - Speech sent from the fort on the Ohio to the Governors of Virginia and Pennsylvania, 1754 April 18 (Box 3, Folder 36-38)
  - Resolution to build forts for the wives and children of both Indians and whites who may go to war for England, New York, 1754 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Letter from Governor James De Lancey to Governor [James] Hamilton, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1754 April 27 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Letter from Governor Robert Dinwiddie to Governor [James] Hamilton, Williamsburg, 1754 April 27 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Letter from Conrad Weiser to Governor James Hamilton, Heidelberg, Berks County, 1754 May 2 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Letter from Governor Robert Dinwiddie to Governor [James] Hamilton, Williamsburg, 1754 July 31 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Speech by Robert Hunter Morris, Lieutenant Governor of Pennsylvania to the Indians of the Six Nations, Delawares, and Shawnees, 1754 November 15 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Speech of Major General William Shirley to the sachems and warriors of the Indians of the Six Nations, [1755 December] (Box 3, Folder 45-46)
  - Letter from Major General William Shirley to Major General Johnson, New York, 1755 December 7 (Box 3, Folder 45-46)
  - Minutes of Council at Philadelphia, 1755 August 7-22 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - News of the Indians, French, and English in Ohio, 1754 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Petition to Lieutenant Governor Robert Morris of Pennsylvania with copies of letters, 1755 October 20 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Letter from John Harris to Benjamin Franklin, Paxton, Pennsylvania, 1755 October 31 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Letter from Samuel Wright to Isaac Norris, 1755 November 2 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Letters from Timothy Horsfield to William Edmonds, Bethlehem, Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Letters from William Parsons to Conrad Weiser and from Adam Hoops to Isaac Norris regarding Indian massacres, 1755 November 3 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Letter from James Wright to a "Worthy Friend" regarding Indian massacres (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Minutes of Council at Philadelphia, 1755 November 8 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1755 August 7 and 15 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1755 August 18 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1755 August 20 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1755 August 20 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1755 August 22 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Testimony regarding Indian troubles, circa 1755 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Minutes of Council of War held by General William Shirley, New York, 1755 December 12-13 (Box 3, Folder 50-54)
  - Minutes of the Council of War (second session), New York, 1755 December 12-13 (Box 3, Folder 50-54)
  - Instructions of Robert Hunter Morris to one of the Oneida chiefs, and Andrew Montour, 1755 November 13 (Box 3, Folder 50-54)
  - Letters from Gideon Hawley to Governor Morris, 1755 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 50-54)
  - Minutes of Council of War, New York, 1755 December 12-13 (Box 3, Folder 50-54)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1756 March 27 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1756 April 8 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Extract of letter from Sir Charles Hardy to Governor Morris, 1756 April 29 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Minutes of the Council at Philadelphia, 1756 June 8 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Memorandum account of Indian conspiracies, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Extract of letter from Sir Charles Hardy to Governor Morris, 1756 April 16 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Reply of James Logan in response to comments made about him by Camassatego regarding the 1742 treaty, circa 1742 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Series V. Original letters, 1560-1781, [967] (Volume 2)
  The series “Original Letters, 1560-1781” contains eighty letters relating to a miscellany of topics and persons, including Scottish poet Tobias Smollett, natural history, the Colonial Committee of Correspondence, the Revolutionary War, and the Pennsylvania Line Revolt of 1781. The most heavily documented topic in this series is the Pennsylvania Line Revolt, a Revolutionary War rebellion in which the Continental Army soldiers rebelled against the Continental Army because of grievances pertaining to poor conditions and supplies. The Pennsylvania Line revolt began on January 1, 1781 and ended on January 29, 1781. The documents include correspondence relating to the mutiny, propositions from the Continental Army for redressing the soldiers’ grievances, proposals from the British Army asking for allegiance from the Pennsylvania Line, trial accounts, and other documents about potential and realized spies for the British.
  The documents are arranged by topic. Many documents were hand copied by Du Simitière from originals. While the date that all of the copies were made is unknown, the dates of the original documents from which copies were made span the years 1560 to 1781. The language of the Du Simitière materials in this series are in English and French.
  It is essential for researchers to know that the first seven letters in the volume were mistakenly bound in this volume and do not belong in the Du Simitière collection. Instead, these letters belong to the Henry Cox collection, which no longer resides at the Library Company. These letters are in Italian.
  - Original Papers relating to the Revolt of the Pennsylvania Line, 1781 January, 1560-1781 (Volume 2, Item 50-77)
- Series VI. Papers relating to the West Indies, 1748-1773; [968] (Box 4)
  The series “Papers relating to the West Indies” contains thirty-nine items about the history of the West Indies, particularly Jamaica and Santo Domingo. The documents within this series contain information on African slave uprisings, rebellions, conspiracies, and the slave trade. There are watercolors and sketches done by Du Simitière in Kingston, Jamaica that include musicians, scenic views, and a street view of two black slaves on the gallows. Other documents of interest include information on the Jamaican-Creole vocabulary, including translations of vocabulary; proverbs in Creole, English, and French; and descriptions, in French, of Java, Batavia, Jamaica, St. Eustatius, Cuba, and Santo Domingo. There are also extracts of many works and letters, lists, maps, sketches, and notes.
  Presumably, this material was collected for a history of the West Indies, and this material is potentially an extension of the series “Papers relating to Natural History.” Many original documents were hand copied by Du Simitière. While the date that the copies were made is unknown, the dates of the original documents from which the copies were made span the years 1748 to 1773. Also included are some of Du Simitière’s original works regarding his personal travels to the West Indies.
  The current order of the documents is presumably the order in which the documents were previously bound. Documents appear to be arranged by topic, including, in this order, descriptions of various islands and voyages, information and history on Jamaica, information and history on Santo Domingo, and general histories of the West Indies. The documents are mostly in French, but some documents are in Jamaican-Creole and English.
  - "Description des Isles de la Sonde," 1741, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Des Manieres de Compteu and des Monnoyer des Isles du Vent and Sous le Vent", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Drawings of Hispaniola Island and St. Domingo City coat of Arms, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
  - "Remarques sur la Havane", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
  - Description of a journey from Leogane, 1773, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Diary of a sea voyage from Amsterdam to St. Eustache, 1757-1758 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Description de L'Isle de Saint Eustache", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Notes on History of Jamaica, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Important events in Jamaica after du Simitière's arrival, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 9-10b)
  - "Vocabulario Creole", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 9-10b)
  - "Explication de quelques termes différens du Français, en usage, aux Isles de l'Amérique, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 9-10b)
  - Creole idioms, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 10c)
  - "Jamaica-Creol", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Papiaminteer creal of Curaao", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 10e)
  - "Extrait du Manuscrit de M.S. sur les remèdes aux maladies de St. Pom", 1758 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Books and maps relating to Jamaica, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sacking of Yaguana, Santo Domingo, 1600, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "Jamaica Chronology," 1492-1750, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "Satire sur Quelques personnes des plus éminentes and des plus Connues de l'Isle de Jamaique", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "Ancient Descriptions of Jamaica;" "Indian Antiquities," 1612, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Extracts from The History of Jamaica or a General Survey of the Ancient and Modern State of that Island, 1774, circa 1775 (Box 4)
  - Alphabetical list of plants in the synopsis of The History of Jamaica or a General Survey of the Ancient and Modern State of that Island, 1774, circa 1775 (Box 4)
  - Coat of Arms of Jamaica, undated (Box 4, Folder 19a)
  - Extracts from works about uprising of Negroes against whites in Jamaica, 1733-1745 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
  - Extract of letter "from a Gentleman", 1760 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
  - "Negroes Conspiracies in several parts of the West Indies and of North America", circa 1770 (Box 4, Folder 22-25)
  - Note on exportation of sugar and importation of Negro slaves in Jamaica, taken from American Weekly Mercury, circa 1729-1730 (Box 4, Folder 22-25)
  - Notes and chronology on Jamaica, 1494-1774, 1740, 1742 (Box 4, Folder 22-25)
  - "Books relating to the West India Islands and Continent", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 22-25)
  - "Coats of arms of some of the Governors of the Island of Jamaica," 1724, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
  - "Origine de l'établissement des Français dans St. Domingue", circa 1773 (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
  - "De la ville and du quartier de Léogâne", circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - "Fragment d'une Chanson faites sur les officiers qui qui était dans le Fort St. Louis a St. Domingue," 1748, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 29-30)
  - Ink sketch of a woman, circa 1775 (Box 4, Folder 29-30)
  - "Extrait du Registre tenu par le notaire and Substitut du Procureur du Roi a Léogane, 1770 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - "Extrait des Registres du Conseil Supérieur du Port au Prince," 1770 (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
  - "Extrait des minutes du Greffe du Siège Royal du Port au Prince," 1773 (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
  - "De la Plaine de Léogane," extract from Labat's Nouveau Voyage, 1742 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Extracts from work regarding the history of the West Indies, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 37-38)
  - Extracts from work regarding the history of the West Indies, 1763 (Box 4, Folder 37-38)
  - Extract regarding the discovery and description of North America, 1770 (Box 4, Folder 39a-39b)
  - Attitude of Reverend Radman toward Quakers, extract from the Mercure de France, 1770 (Box 4, Folder 39a-39b)
- Series VII. Original Journals and Extracts, [1411.Q] (Box 5)
  The series “Original Journals and Extracts” contains twenty items relating to a miscellany of topics including journals of expeditions and travels to the Susquehanna and Ottawa, notes and accounts of General John Sullivan’s Western expedition, extracts from travel accounts of Captain Cook in the Pacific and Thurberg's account of Japan, documents about a variety of expeditions, and extracts from newspapers, poems, and documents relating to or by the poet John Maylem. The journals of the John Sullivan expedition document the expedition, but they also include several wash drawings of Indian dwellings and writings. Other poets included in this series are Nicholas Skull, a Pennsylvania surveyor, and Reverend Thomas Hopkinson. Some curiosities in this series include two extracts from the Mercure de France, one about a woman with a horn on her hand and another about a woman who apparently spontaneously combusted.
  Many documents are extracted copies or full copies of original documents done by Du Simitière. While the date that the copies were made is unknown, the dates of the original documents from which the copies were made span the years 1629 to 1782. The current order of the documents is presumably the order in which the documents were previously bound. Documents appear to be arranged by topic.
  - "Notes of a Tour to the Head of the Susquehanna in the Year 1769", 1780 October (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Journal of a trading expedition up the Roiviere des Lievres, or Riviere des Outaovais in Canada," 1775, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Extract from journal of General John Sullivan's Western Expedition kept by William Pierce, 1769-1779, undated (Box 5, Folder 3a-3b)
  - Journal of General Sullivan's Western Expedition kept by Dr. Charles MacArthur, 1779, undated (Box 5, Folder 3a-3b)
  - "Chronology of what relates to the Indian Wars in North America," 1751-1779, undated (Box 5, Folder 4a)
  - A Short Memorandum and the names and distances of the places that the 4th Pennsylvania. Regt. march'd thro' in the year 1779, undated (Box 5, Folder 5e)
  - Names of the towns through which the Western army marched taken from General Sullivan's letter from Pennsylvania Packet 1779, undated (Box 5, Folder 5a-5d)
  - Notes on General Sullivan's Western Expedition against the Iroquois, undated (Box 5, Folder 5a-5d)
  - Route of General Sullivan's Army from Easton, Pennsylvania, to Genesee, 1779, undated (Box 5, Folder 5a-5d)
  - Memorandum by John Devitor, soldier in Sullivan's Expedition, undated (Box 5, Folder 5a-5d)
  - Memorandum of places 4th Pennsylvania Regiment marched through in Sullivan's Expedition, kept by soldier John Allison, 1778-1779, undated (Box 5, Folder 5e)
  - Drawing of order of march and battle of Major General Sullivan's Army on the Western Expedition, 1779, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chart of the discoveries made by Captain Cook and other European navigators in the Pacific Ocean, from the London Magazine, 1780 December (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "A summary Account of the Voyage of the late Captain James cook undertaken by order of the British Government," 1776-1782, undated (Box 5, Folder 8a-8b)
  - "Accounts of the Russian Discoveries between Asia and America," 1780-1781, undated (Box 5, Folder 8a-8b)
  - "Curious Account of the inhabitants of the Empire of Japan, their Government, Manners, and Customs," 1775, 1780, undated (Box 5, Folder 8c-9)
  - "New Voyages," brief extract from Mercure de France, 1782 August 10 (Box 5, Folder 8c-9)
  - "Account of the Royal Cabinet of Natural History at Madrid," extracted from John Talbot Dillon's Travels through Spain, 1780, undated (Box 5, Folder 8c-9)
  - "Peinture Etudorique," extract from Gazette d'Agriculture, Commerce, Finances, et Arts, 1782 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 10a-11b)
  - "Secret pour faire reparoitre les couleurs des Tableaux," extract from Gazette d'Agriculture, Commerce, finances et Arts, 1782 June 19 (Box 5, Folder 10a-11b)
  - Account of a woman with a horn on her right hand, extracted from Mercure de France, 1782 July 6 (Box 5, Folder 10a-11b)
  - Account of a woman burned to death, extracted from Mercure de France, 1782 July 13 (Box 5, Folder 10a-11b)
  - "On seeing a wedding at the revd. Mr. Com--s on Monday last" comic verse from American Weekly Mercury, 1729 June 19 (Box 5, Folder 12a-12e)
  - "The Sorrowful Lamentation of Samuel keimer, printer of the Barbados Gazette," extract from the Pennsylvania Gazette, 1734 September 25 (Box 5, Folder 12a-12e)
  - "The Poet's lamentation for the Loss of His Cat, whom he us'd to call his Muse", undated (Box 5, Folder 12a-12e)
  - "On Mr. B_____s's Singing a Hymn of His Own Composing," by Jo. Green, 1756 April 1 (Box 5, Folder 12a-12e)
  - "The Taking of Montreal" by Mr. Gamble, undated (Box 5, Folder 12a-12e)
  - "An elegy occasioned by the death of Romeo", 1779 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "Dirtilla," by unknown author, undated (Box 5, Folder 14a-14b)
  - "The Treaty", 1761 (Box 5, Folder 14a-14b)
  - "Satire on Halifax", undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "The Boston Sabbath", undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "An Acrostick," by John Mayhem, undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "Epitaph of Benjamin Franklin Esqr," by Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "Pennsylvania," by George Watt, 1730 (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - Extracts from a "Book of Poesies", undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - Poem by John Maylem written on his twenty-first birthday, April 30, 1760, undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "The Birdiad," by John Maylem, undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "John Maylem's directions to his Taylor in New York," by John Maylem, undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "Acrostic," by John Maylem to Polly Turner, undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "The Daw and Peacocks," by John Maylem, undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - "To Mr. Harris in the Fields", undated (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - Letter from "Blanco" to Mr. Maylem, Livingston's Manour, 1759 June 2 (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - Letter from John Maylem to "Blanco", New York, 1759 June 15 (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - Letter from John Maylem to Mr. J[o]s[e]phs[ o]n, Newport, 1760 October 15 (Box 5, Folder 15a-17d)
  - Parody made by John Tabor Kemp, attorney general of New Jersey, 1776 February (Box 5, Folder 18)